Twilight [music] Sparkle, my most
faithful student, gaze upon these
massive orange balls. Do you know where
we are? An orange orchard [music] behind
Canterlot Castle.
Wrong. It is my orange orchard, which is
different than a normal one. These
orange [music] trees grow with pinpoint
accuracy directly under the sun. The
[__] ton of trees you see before you are
[music] in this exact spot only because
I decided they should. So yes, it's a
bit more than an orchard. Wow, no wonder
the sun looks like [music] an orange.
Now my [__] I cleared time to pick
oranges with you. Do you understand how
rare that is for me?
>> [music]
>> Yeah, I mean you do a lot of stuff. Yes,
I run a whole country of stupid little
ponies. And yet I thought, you know
what? I'll step away from all of that
for one afternoon [music] and spend it
with Twilight. Which is why I expect you
to appreciate it appropriately. If you
do well enough, I may [music] let you
take an orange that I touched home as a
souvenir. Because I touched it, it is
now worth 42 trillion bucks. Such things
touched by me carry much weight [music]
in this world.
Yes, ma'am.
I'm going to get a bucket to carry the
oranges back to my 806 trillion-dollar
castle.
>> [music]
>> I'd like to actually pick the oranges
together with you, my best friend. So
just stand here and wait [music] for me.
Legend say Princess Celestia's oranges
are really plump and juicy. As expected,
only she can grow such an exquisite
[music] thing. I mean, she didn't say I
couldn't have one.
Sweet Celestia, [music]
it's so wet it's like Princess Celestia
herself just peed in my mouth. You know
[music] what? Maybe I should have
another one just to check for
consistency.
Twilight, my loyal friend, I [music]
have returned.
Twilight Sparkle, where did my 40-acre
orange orchard go? Princess Celestia, I
I can explain.
Save it, Twilight. For I am truly
saddened by the fact that you clearly
hate me so much you would resort to
gorging yourself on over 700 oranges
just to avoid spending one afternoon
with me.
7,000.
What? You said 700, but 7,000 is the
established term for that amount.
This is why no one invites you over to
their house.
>> [crying]
>> Hey, horse. Want to see something that's
at least 20% cooler than that baby's
wipeout? Oh, boy. Are you going to [__]
your pants?
>> [cheering]
>> Why did you blast ass? Couldn't you have
just flapped your wings instead since
you're a pegasus? Yeah, Rainbow Dash,
that that was just strange as [__]
Twilight Sparkle, come down here.
I require a moment of your time.
I can see you are having fun at the
skate park with the rest of your [__]
brigade. Fun is an overstatement, but
yes, you are correct that I am in their
company at the moment. Well, I want you
to call my sister and invite her over to
play with you.
No way. She choked me and slammed me
against a tree. You don't get it, girl.
You made Princess Celestia mad, and when
Celestia gets mad, she doesn't let me
watch movies on my 32-in Roku.
Do you know what happens when I don't
get to watch my movies on my Roku TV?
No. I do bad things. Do you know how bad
I can get? I got banned on Xbox Live.
Everyone gets banned on Xbox Live. In
2008.
Please don't hurt me. Holy [__] who's
that batty threatening Twilight? That's
the other princess, Princess Luna.
We have two of them? She's just
embarrassed to go outside because she's
black. Hey, Pinkie need some help?
See, balance is key. If you don't put
your hoof in the right place, you're
going to end up falling off.
Your hair smells like strawberries. Did
you get a new shampoo by chance? Oh my
god, Rainbow Dash is grabbing Pinkie
Pie's butt. That's so gay.
Shut up Lyra. No, I No, I wasn't. She's
gay. Rainbow Dash is gay. I'm going to
kill you, Lyra.
You okay, sugar tits? No, didn't you
see? Rainbow Dash was going to kiss me,
but she chickened out. Okay. Is it
because I am severely mentally
handicapped that Rainbow Dash is
embarrassed of me? Yep. Rarity, I don't
want to skate anymore today, so I'm
going home. Okay.
Mrs. Cake, I'm back from the skate park.
Can I help you feed the babies? You're
not my real daughter, Pinkie Pie. I just
found you on the doorstep one rainy
afternoon covered in your own gross
piss. I will never let you near these
babies because you are not a proper
member of the cake family. I allow you
to work here and sleep in the basement
upstairs exclusively between the times
of 10:00 p.m. at night and 4:00 in the
morning. But, that is as far as our
familial relationship will ever go. Get
out of my house. You're not allowed in
unless it's work hours.
Hey, [__] Yeah, you with the really
fat butt. Oh, hi Rosie. How are you? I
just got out of rehab for for the
kidnapping of a 6-year-old boy. But
aside from that, I'm pissed off because
you stepped on a flower.
And I you know, I love flowers almost
twice as much as colts.
So, I think we got a problem here,
[__]
Also, I can smell that you like changed
your shampoo to strawberry from
lavender, which is a flower. So, I'm
going to have to kick your butt. Daisy,
get behind her so she doesn't run away.
I know it's going to be hard to squeeze
back there since her ass cheeks are
massive and this alleyway is small, but
we got to work with what we got. Lily,
you just keep standing to the left
looking sexy. God, you're so
good-looking. I wish you were a colt.
That flower you stepped on took weeks to
grow, you pink bimbo. In Ponyville,
where horses casually eat flowers, it
beat all the odds and made it to full
bloom and you crushed it without even
looking. How would you like it if some
pony did that to you, huh, [__]
Please, have mercy. You don't deserve
mercy, [__] You tore off all of that
sunflower's petals, so we're going to
cut your hair off.
Please, no. I'll do anything.
Anything? I think something can be
arranged then.
Lap up my salty warm piss and I just may
forget how you stepped on that poor
innocent flower. Look, she's going for
it. Haha, what a loser. No wonder they
call you Pinkie, like pee. Drink that
pee, [__] After this, they'll be
calling her pee pee pie or better yet,
pee pee poop after I make her eat my
[__]
Stop throwing bricks at the great and
powerful Trixie's wagon. THIS IS A
RENTAL.
>> [laughter]
>> THOSE DUMB BRATS.
>> [music]
>> THEY'RE LUCKY Trixie is trapped within
shadows of night. Trixie should invest
in a gun.
Curses, Bell. You're getting salsagheti
all over my equipment. Oh, sorry.
The great and powerful Trixie requires
competence, [music] Bell, and she is
hastily beginning to regret hiring you
on Craigslist. What do these smoke
[music] bombs do? It's a smoke bomb. The
answer is in the title, little [__]
Put it in the box with the [music] rest.
>> Okay.
Lord have mercy.
Also, we're moving the Trixie part
[music] in your name. The great and
powerful Trixie cannot be upstaged by
having her personal assistant share her
first name. So, you're going by Bell
now. It sounds like ball, and it'll make
you look like a bottom and my [music]
personal [__] Like all you do is suck
balls. I'm starting to see why everyone
in town calls you a douchebag. Good.
That means my brand is working. Hey,
isn't that Sparkle's friend, the pink
one who is on the sex offender's
registry? This is Ponyville, Bell.
Everyone is on the registry. I'm not.
Being unique does not make you cool. Go
package up my smoke [music] bombs before
I stick them up
Get away from her. Yeah, before I throw
Bell at your head like a basketball.
[music] And you're not black, so I know
you won't be able to catch him or dodge
him. I had no idea the circus was in
town. Some pony better let everyone know
a couple of clowns blew away. Like, oh
my god, look at that grown ass man. He's
so short. Is he really challenging us to
a fight? They're already prejudging me.
Open the wagon and let me back in. I
can't. I parked in direct sunlight.
[music]
If I open the door, I might burst into
flames and explode because I'm a stupid
vampire.
Look at him go. Trying to be all brave
and [__] Gosh darn it, Trixie Bell. You
are a 1,000-year-old man. Assert [music]
that guilt energy. What are you doing?
Trixie is right. So, put Put me down. I
am a big, strong stallion that only
happens to be of a small and cute
stature. I demand to be feared.
>> [bell]
>> Oh my god, he even jingles. I want to
take him home. Give that back to me.
It's mine. Look at him hop for it like a
little bunny. Hey Rose, you should so
take a dump in his hat.
Lilly, pick this man up off the floor.
He needs a good [__] slap across the
cheeks. Come on, man. Y'all don't got to
do this, not in front of ALL THESE
GIRLS.
>> [laughter]
>> I AM SO BORED BEATING UP PEOPLE with
autism. Come on, girls. We've got actual
things to do, like planting flowers.
Hell yeah, I love flowers. Flowers are
some real gangster [__] Well, you saved
me. No, I didn't. I just got humiliated.
Yeah, but you used your perfectly
rounded, poundable ass to pull the
bullying away from me, and that's what
matter.
My friend Dashie liked my shampoo, but I
don't think she wants to be seen
smelling it.
>> And tell her how that made you feel,
because if she doesn't realize she hurt
you, nothing's going to change. But what
if she just don't give a [__] She's not
worth your time, but something tells me
you're wrong. Yeah, I know. I just don't
give a [__] You don't seriously think I
put my whole image on the line for a
[__] Rainbow Dash knows her worth.
That's why she splurges and buys Bush's
baked beans over Heinz cuz it costs
more. I thought you prefer Bush's baked
beans.
Everyone does, but I mostly just get it
to one-up everyone at tailgate parties.
Look, Twilight, my sister is here. What
do you want, you orange stealer? Why did
you call me over on our Android phones?
I wanted to know if you wanted to skate
with me. Skateboarding is some crusty
white people [__] and as you know, I am
a god, which is not that much different
from a white person, but nevertheless,
what What think if they saw their
overlord rolling around on something as
primitive as a skateboard? I think they
would respect you more because it makes
you seem less narcissistic and
self-centered. But I am narcissistic and
self-centered. It's how you win at life.
Have you ever met a good billionaire?
Twilight Sparkle, get out of my way.
What are you going to do if I don't?
Drop a burning chunk of rock like the
sun on me. I've been through worse. I
don't think you realize, fool. There are
over 10 sextillion suns, including the
red supergiant one, Stephenson 2-18,
which is so goddamn large that 10
billion of our own suns can fit inside
of it.
>> [laughter]
>> Sex-sextillion?
Like the word sex? Why is that funny?
It's just a number on the numerical
scale like million, billion, and
trillion. Oh my god, Twilight, you're so
annoying. And that's not counting the
suns outside our known universe. Do you
know how many there truly are?
Me neither, but I can assure you it is
far more than six.
Six? Six sounds like sex, too.
That's it. I'm turning the sun off.
You're all going in a 15-minute timeout.
Celestia, turn the sun back on. You're
just being an [__]
Twilight, my friend, what has become of
you? The universe became impossibly
cold, so life came to an abrupt halt.
All beings frozen in time, you dumb ass.
Twilight, get out of there and worship
me. I want a skateboard. She can't hear
you anymore for she is but a really big
ice cube.
Why aren't you frozen? My heart is
already cold as ice. Damn. Mayor of emo
town over here.
Okay, Twilight, you have won me over. I
will give you another chance to not be a
complete and utter waste of my
breathable air. Later tonight, I am
holding a party. Do you know the Palms
Casino Resort in Las Vegas? That's the
most expensive hotel in the world. Yeah,
well, my party is going to be next door
to that building in the Best Western
because they have more relaxed security.
So, me and my friends will be able to
party for a few hours until they
inevitably kick us out for being too
epic and bombastic.
Look, Celestia's already here and she
has a bowl of fruit.
I don't see any orange slices in that
fruit salad. It's probably because I ate
them all. Let's go.
Where's her friends? You said she was
inviting friends. I reckon she was
talking about us. You can't just throw a
party here in the lobby. Either rent a
room or get out. [__] shut up. You're
acting like this is the Palms Casino
Resort. This is a Best Western.
Sorry, Twilight. I thought the Best
Western employees would be cool with it.
I guess the party's over. Go tell your
friends to go home.
Hey, Princess Celestia.
>> [music]
>> I want to apologize about your party. Do
not blame yourself, my [__] The fault
lies upon the Best [music] Western
company who failed to recognize my
importance. Imagine if Jesus Christ
returned to the world and immediately
went to Popeye's [music] for a chicken
sandwich and they refused to give him
one for free. That is basically what
transpired here today. But, I can't help
but think about how if I didn't eat all
of your oranges this morning, we would
be having fun together [music] in your
orchard, just the two of us picking
oranges.
You must be so mad. Again, [music] I'll
have to point fingers at the Best
Western company because those oranges
were going to be served at the party in
a really big bowl [music] of fruit
salad. So, we would have wasted our time
to begin with and I bet I would have
been more mad than I am now. So, in a
way you did a good thing.
Hey, Princess. [music]
I know something fun we can do together.
Haha, you're right, Twilight. That was
pretty thrilling. I feel like a rebel.
Yes, I read a book how destroying
objects and places associated with
emotional distress can trigger feelings
of excitement. Look, there's some
ponies. Let's go murder them.
Don't worry, my apprentice. They won't
arrest the god of their world.
Jesus said, "If the world hates you,
remember it hated him first. If we
belong to the world, then the world
would love us as its own. But, it
doesn't. Therefore, we do not belong to
it. That is why the world hates us."
Okay, your bond is $8.
That's way too much. As the current
monarch of Equestria, I am creating a
new ordinance that cuts all jail bonds
by 80% and it takes effect immediately.
Here's $3 for mine and Twilight's
release from prison. They won't kick up
to much of a fuss over the missing
dollar because I am Princess Celestia.
Look, the sun is about to set. Yes, my
friend. Now is the time for my ugly
sister to take over and I shall return
to my castle to eat two cans of Hormel
tamales and watch movies on my 32-in
Roku TV because I am rich enough to
afford one.
Why is there five here? Did they
seriously skim me out of a whole tamale?
Celestia, shouldn't you be asleep? Don't
talk to me, Luna. I'm making tamales
because I had a really [__] day. So, I
need to end it off with the highest note
I can. Get me the shredded Fiesta blend
and Tapatio from the fridge.
I know. That's why I was wondering if
you'd like to get off your ass and do
something fun together. It will be my
treat. Inside language, Luna. He is
listening.
What is this? Why is it filled with
balls? It's bubble tea. You sip it and
there's little chewy things at the
bottom. Well, it's different and I don't
like things that are different. I want
chocolate milk. I want to drink it with
a bendy straw.
This is bad. If I don't do something,
she's going to end up going home.
Whatever I say next will decide the fate
of this date.
Do you remember that time we filled the
bathtub [music] with dried egg powder
mix and swam around in scrambled eggs?
No. Oh, yeah. That was just me because
mom and dad gave you all of the
attention. I'm going home.
Hey, do you want to go dream hopping?
What's that? When I'm bored, I like to
jump into ponies' dreams [music] and
observe their deep thoughts. Do you want
to come with me? Yes. It will be an
excellent way to determine which pony
should be exterminated for not
worshiping me enough.
This is Pinkie Pie's dream world. She
usually dreams some screwed [music] up
fetish [__]
Hi. Do you want to buy a cupcake?
Oh, she's just dreaming about [music]
selling cakes. Let's go to another one.
She's fast.
I know you've been sneaking into my
dreams, Luna, at least three times a
week. That's really mean and invasion of
privacy, so I laid a trap for you.
I took approximately 53 sleeping pills
tonight to make sure nothing would wake
me up until the next morning. [__] She
laid a trap for us. If only I could
reach my dream gun I stuffed in my butt
crack. Should I grab it? No, then you
might touch my butt and that would be
gay. We'll just use this portal to leave
instead.
She escaped through the Pinkie Pie sized
hole after her.
You idiot, you made the portal [music]
too short for my long ass neck. Sucks to
be you.
Oh no, I can't get through either
because of my wide load dump truck.
Celestia, that Pinkie is a dream pony,
which means she can do anything the real
Pinkie Pie can dream of.
The only way to get rid of her is to
either wake Pinkie Pie up so she'll
disappear or force her back into the
world of dreams.
Luckily, Pinkie Pie's mental retardation
is so severe that though she could
theoretically destroy the world in a
nanosecond, she doesn't realize it. For
the first time in Equestrian history,
mental illness has saved the world.
I'm going to kill the real [music]
Pinkie Pie and take her place. Stop
following me. We can't let you do that
dream Pinkie. Go back into the dream
right now. [music] No. Then I will pull
a moon from a distant galaxy to throw at
you.
>> [music]
>> Let's see you handle this.
She used her imagination to grow bigger.
She's the size of like eight Pinkie Pies
standing [music] on each other's
shoulders.
Ah!
Who are you? I can't [music] see your
face. It's Princess Celestia. A dream
version of Pinkie Pie has escaped from
an alternative dimension and [music] she
ate Luna. It is imperative that you let
me borrow a gun from your super cool gun
rack.
It disappeared.
I guess dream Pinkie Pie knew I would
get a gun, so she erased guns from the
world just now. Celestia, isn't there
[music] anything we can do? Nothing you
can do my friend. Stay here and seek
refuge in your really big tree for it is
time for me to unleash a really powerful
spell. The same one I used to defeat
Nightmare Moon, Discord, [music]
King Sombra, Lord Tirek, and Cozy Glow,
that one black [__] [music] and Josh
Haber, and a million other villains,
because I'm the only one who can get
[__] done.
Wait here, Twilight. [music] It is time
for me to drag my balls across that pink
bitch's face. Look, it's Princess
Celestia. She's going [music] to save us
all. Save us, Princess.
You think you can defeat me, Princess
Celestia? I can do anything.
Shut up, Rarity.
No!
Even you have limits, and your limit is
knowledge. You can fight back as much as
you want, but the sheer number of suns
that I have at my command go far beyond
what [music] a mere horse can even
fathom.
Celestia, [music] you saved me.
You bet your emo ass I did, my little
black cat. Now, let us save Equestria
with the most powerful [music] spell in
the My Little Pony universe.
Look at the size of those guns. [music]
The bullets they fire must be massive.
Oh, no, a bullet that size would be
expensive. So, even though the gun is
the size of multiple continents, the
bullets are the size of normal bullets.
>> [music]
>> Dear Princess Celestia, in other words,
me. Today, I didn't learn any lesson at
all because I was right. I've been
telling all of these little pony [__]
all day long that I am a god, and I
continue to prove it. Yet, I shall
remain a friend to all of these weird
little pony [__] because it makes me
look good. Like when the cool kids at
school befriend the one fat kid who sits
at the back of class because it [music]
gives them an even bigger ego than they
already had before. When the world was
in danger, I was the only one who could
do [__] because I am just that much
better than them. I can't wait to
[music] bring this up again with
Twilight the next time that bratty [__]
gives me attitude.
>> [music]
>> So, I walked out
back before the second
set settled. [singing and music]
My dad I'll miss the rest. That's fine,
I [singing and music] guess. The cabinet
is a crowd around,
but I could scarce get by
on second breath between the press. Now
it's 3:00 a.m.
and I
don't know how
I'll get home.
The way is barely paved.
I can't keep
my
eyes from closing, [music] so
I'll hit
replay.